<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Steve McGrath</title>
    <link>http://stevemcgrath.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Steve McGrath</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Steve McGrath 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://stevemcgrath.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>pyTenable v0.3.3 Released</title>
      <link>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2018-11-30-pytenable-v0.3.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2018-11-30-pytenable-v0.3.3/</guid>
      <description>The pyTenable library has been rapidly evolving over the past few months. The library has seen a lot of expansion and maturation over the last several weeks. Going from version 0.1.0 at the time of last post to now 0.3.3, there has been a lot of work done to lay scaffolding for the SecurityCenter package. SecurityCenter (recently re-branded as Tenable.sc) is as large, if not larger a project as Tenable.io was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pyTenable v0.1.0 Released</title>
      <link>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2018-10-03-pytenable-v0.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2018-10-03-pytenable-v0.1.0/</guid>
      <description>After nearly 8 months of on-and-off development (mostly off, day-job work keeps my busy), I&amp;rsquo;m proud to announce that pyTenable has hit version 0.1.0. While this may not seem like much, it&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of work to bring it across this line in the journey so far. All of the Tenable.io Vulnerability Management API are now pythonized. Further everything in the tenable_io module has been tested out (519 tests!). Tenable has also seen fit to link to pyTenable as an official module for working with our products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Deployment Files Release</title>
      <link>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2016-01-13-initial-deployment-files-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 10:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2016-01-13-initial-deployment-files-release/</guid>
      <description>I have started working through all of the various fabric files I have and started centralizing them and cleaning them up for general consumption. These fabric scripts cover a variety of tasks from deployment and maintenance of various products to deploying some of my code. I will be updating the repository as needs arise, and as always am welcome to any input.
Using my fabric files is actually pretty simple, however you need to have fabric installed on your workstation before anything will work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pySecurityCenter 2.1 Release</title>
      <link>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2015-07-15-pysecuritycenter-2-1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://stevemcgrath.io/post/2015-07-15-pysecuritycenter-2-1-release/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m proud to announce the general availability for pySecurityCenter version 2.1.x accessible from PyPI immediately. pySC 2.1 supports connectivity to SecurityCenter 5, which leverages a completely new RESTful API. Because of this, the pySC SecurityCenter 5 support will be an evolving process. Whats implemented today will not be changing, however many of the convenience functions that pySecurityCenter has for SecurityCenter 4.x have not been coded into the SC5 module, as enumeration for the API is still active.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>